听译：SuperBart   1994年《毁灭战士二代》广告
MAP20 Gotcha! by John Romero
Doom II is just such a bigger, badder, better version of Doom.
毁灭战士二代就是个更大，更邪恶，更好的毁灭战士
A lot of people are waiting here, for sure.
绝对有很多人在期待的
Pretty much more popular than football.
绝对比橄榄球更流行
MAP15 Industrial Zone by John Romero
Once you start playing... you're HOOKED.
绝对是 玩 不 释 手 的
大恶魔Sandy Peterson->
We have a lot of people asking
很多人问我们
what you're expecting DOOM II when they're come out,
对毁灭战士二代的出品有什么期待
where is it going to be, you know, to can buy the game.
哪里可以买到游戏呢
Steam 有卖的，售价18元（G胖的微笑警告）
We knew it was going to be a monster hit,
我们意识到这个游戏绝对会比东方萌妹子火
when the people from GT interactive software
当发行商GT Interactive定下这个计划，并透风说
settle it down and gave us a clue
is to what kind of numbers Doom 2 was doing in pre-orders.
毁灭战士二代预售量的时候
We all hit the floor we couldn't believe it has been nominated
我们高兴得不得了，太难以置信了
MAP26 The Abandoned Mines by John Romero
A lot of retailers are getting demand for Doom II already.
很多零售商点名要进货毁灭战士二代了
So they know that when DOOM II come out,
他们零售商明白，毁灭战士二代出品的时候
they will be able to sell a lot of product.
他们能卖很多，赚到很多钱
I've always dig it the DOOM II when people ask me to describe it.
当人们想让我描述毁灭战士二代的时候，我很高兴的
I say it's bigger, badder and better than DOOM.
要我说，这会比一代更大，更邪恶，更好
The levels will be more expense,
关卡设计更加用心
more fine tuned for multiplayer play.
为多人游戏而精心调教
A level designer's expertise in designing levels will show through because
关卡设计师的设计专长将在新作展现得淋漓尽致
they've learned a lot from the creation of Doom 1 or 'Doom'
因为他们从设计毁灭战士一代的关卡中获得很多经验
and it, uh... their level of expertise will show through in Doom 2.
然后......他们的设计专长将在二代游戏中充分展现
The new weapons, although at this point
还有全新武器，尽管这时
we haven't settled on exactly what those weapons will be,
我们还没定下来武器会有什么
but there be new weapons, new bad guys.
但会有新武器，新敌人的
MAP13 Downtown by Sandy Peterson
Again, bigger, badder, better than DOOM.
最后，这将会比一代更大，更邪恶，更好
These graphics are not better, but it's more...
尽管画面没好多少，但是这个......
It’s not too Nintendoish.
和任天堂的风格很不一样
MAP26 The Abandoned Mines by John Romero
It's great, the graphics are incredible.
好极了，画面看上去很惊艳
And I'm settled by every level now.
我终于通了这些关卡了
Now after these number solve days,
在日常繁重的计算工作后
this is probably the healthy release of tension.
也许这真的是健康的释放压力方式吧
They'll fulfil every time you've put in.
他将会充实你游玩的每一刻
This is fun, I wanna copy this thing home.
很有意思，我想拷一份回家:-)
还不赶紧下载一份呢:-)